[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Who are the five best rappers of all-time?",
      "answer": "Dylan, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jay-Z, Kendrick Lamar, 2pac, Notorious B.I.G., Nas", "Mos Def, Talib Kweli, Black Thought, Big L, Lupe Fiasco", "Lil Pump, Lil Xan, Jack Harlow, Machine Gun Kelly, Ian"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/5HRY4LUl5lc?si=I5tzu1eeAHWNRwcA&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["comedy", "pop culture", "music"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "In the song \"Papa Was A Rollin' Stone\" by The Temptations, what day in September will he always remember?",
      "answer": "3rd",
      "incorrect_answers": ["21st", "15th", "What?"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/71l85z2bXAs?si=RTRzlcFAaofuIJ-m&amp;controls=0&amp;start=233",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["pop culture", "music"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Who is known as the 'King of Pop'?",
      "answer": "Michael Jackson",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Prince", "Usher", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Zi_XLOBDo_Y?si=V9qeX57tq8SQbvm5&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What Beyoncé album features the hit song 'Formation'?",
      "answer": "Lemonade",
      "incorrect_answers": ["4", "B'Day", "Dangerously in Love"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/WDZJPJV__bQ?si=ncgQc4cri-oxHU9p&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which rapper is famous for the album 'The College Dropout'?",
      "answer": "Kanye West",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jay-Z", "Drake", "MC Hammer"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/8kyWDhB_QeI?si=-WbJrIeOztK87mYo&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Who was the first Black woman inducted into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?",
      "answer": "Aretha Franklin",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Tina Turner", "Diana Ross", "Whitney Houston"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/T-fz6TAipqo?si=jCr3gzRAdQRedLOC&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What jazz musician is known for 'What a Wonderful World'?",
      "answer": "Louis Armstrong",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Duke Ellington", "Miles Davis", "Elvis Presley"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/VqhCQZaH4Vs?si=35D_sYzQCPJpED2P&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which hip-hop duo released the classic album 'Stankonia'?",
      "answer": "OutKast",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Run-D.M.C.", "The Neptunes", "Milli Vanilli"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/MYxAiK6VnXw?si=jLWVXZQOQ_zgJYzA&amp;controls=0&amp;start=8",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Who is referred to as the 'Queen of Hip-Hop Soul'?",
      "answer": "Mary J. Blige",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Lauryn Hill", "Missy Elliott", "Cardi B"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Nia2C6JW4VU?si=_YcAF_CmJZgPM4h2&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "What is the name of Rihanna’s beauty brand?",
      "answer": "Fenty Beauty",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Riri Glow", "Savage Fenty", "Barbados Glam"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/e82VE8UtW8A?si=w1o3Te5fSS-kHDSe&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["pop culture", "business"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What group did Michael Jackson belong to as a child?",
      "answer": "The Jackson 5",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Temptations", "The Commodores", "The Rolling Stones"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/y2bVIBwpCTA?si=J7EZHaQxd7WtT2lE&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Which rapper famously coined the phrase 'Y’all gon’ make me lose my mind'?",
      "answer": "DMX",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Busta Rhymes", "Snoop Dogg", "Bill Nye"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/thIVtEOtlWM?si=LgqhnNhZoVgBbcDV&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Who was the first Black actor to win an Academy Award for Best Actor?",
      "answer": "Sidney Poitier",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Denzel Washington", "Morgan Freeman", "Kevin Hart"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/RwMgEM9FNhE?si=I99jaAUXDzWtTupY&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What 2018 superhero film broke box office records with a predominantly Black cast?",
      "answer": "Black Panther",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Luke Cage", "Blade", "The Dark Knight"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/HEpiVXbBUBw?si=Y1wOFC-Pk1lWejet&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "Who directed the film 'Training Day'?",
      "answer": "Antoine Fuqua",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Forest Whitaker", "Ryan Coogler", "Tyler Perry"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/V_CPlOURy1U?si=PAFpxFYX-jvBW-3D&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "What movie featured Angela Bassett and Laurence Fishburne as Tina and Ike Turner?",
      "answer": "What's Love Got to Do with It",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ray", "Dreamgirls", "Avatar"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/XuXqDzUlzi0?si=kHwDu6TL8rEH75kO&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "What film features the quote, 'Bye, Felicia'?",
      "answer": "Friday",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Barbershop", "House Party", "Gone with the Wind"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/5ZALQf6MiOo?si=MdMSIUnNAFOYS8Jv&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "Which actress starred in 'Hidden Figures', 'Empire', and 'Baby Boy'?",
      "answer": "Taraji P. Henson",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Viola Davis", "Octavia Spencer", "Meryl Streep"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/nbvWmgFMQUo?si=S1qEYX8FAr6jfzdr&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "What movie stars Eddie Murphy as Prince Akeem?",
      "answer": "Coming to America",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Trading Places", "The Nutty Professor", "The Lion King"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Aoe-Vrs3-oE?si=hudN4wfwLBwWOwfw&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "What civil rights era film was directed by Ava DuVernay in 2014?",
      "answer": "Selma",
      "incorrect_answers": ["12 Years a Slave", "The Help", "Batman Begins"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Pt6zM9s1cjw?si=6zxpdVqN288E9uv-&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "Who played the main antagonist of the movie 'Black Panther'?",
      "answer": "Michael B. Jordan",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Chadwick Boseman", "Idris Elba", "Chris Evans"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/4MVQXdtrEQM?si=wPZY7aFXPHY8N-eR&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "What 1992 biographical film features Denzel Washington?",
      "answer": "Malcolm X",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ali", "Glory", "Boyz n the Hood"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/VNOJI_DUVn8?si=oMJRDeFJletABaXi&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "What sitcom featured the Huxtable family?",
      "answer": "The Cosby Show",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Family Matters", "Good Times", "Friends"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/NqivLvvg_Mo?si=YPGedxGBCyLeDD4P&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "Who is the longest-running cast member on 'Saturday Night Live'?",
      "answer": "Kenan Thompson",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Chris Rock", "Eddie Murphy", "Dave Chappelle"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/sqpnRyfz_aY?si=Ckgvpvqey5XEPTOq&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "What show launched Issa Rae’s career on HBO?",
      "answer": "Insecure",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Misadventures of Awkward Black Girl", "A Black Lady Sketch Show", "Euphoria"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/t8ypc-JnpV0?si=o28_dMki6B5La3vS&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "Who played the character Gina in 'Martin'?",
      "answer": "Tisha Campbell",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Tichina Arnold", "Regina King", "Halle Berry"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/iWI-entVgPs?si=pYEepH9jxRkyC5Gy&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "What animated series features Huey and Riley Freeman?",
      "answer": "The Boondocks",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Static Shock", "Young Justice", "SpongeBob SquarePants"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/2sHEw6f-Uy8?si=ifZYOGwzDE_mm-V3&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "What is the name of the spin-off series of 'Black-ish' featuring Zoey Johnson?",
      "answer": "Grown-ish",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mixed-ish", "College-ish", "Young-ish"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/iN9NVMPoHRs?si=9i-Kn8dxpD5qH0fx&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "What 90s sitcom was set at the fictional Hillman College?",
      "answer": "A Different World",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Living Single", "Sister, Sister", "Saved by the Bell"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/cnWlmFLJvbU?si=LMwRzTsTXr2ukw7i&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "Who played Olivia Pope in 'Scandal'?",
      "answer": "Kerry Washington",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Viola Davis", "Taraji P. Henson", "Gabrielle Union"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/db0nJKgd__g?si=4Jvnzn5vsjjWAtm4&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "drama"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "What talk show did Oprah Winfrey host for 25 years?",
      "answer": "The Oprah Winfrey Show",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The View", "Ellen", "The Jerry Springer Show"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/bbm6IXyEc0g?si=5piO7ro9av7FEXEb&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "Which comedy duo created the sketch comedy show 'Key & Peele'?",
      "answer": "Jordan Peele & Keegan-Michael Key",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Eddie Murphy & Arsenio Hall", "Dave Chappelle & Charlie Murphy", "Chris Rock & Wanda Sykes"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/CoFjr3pgjCg?si=-kIbw803dOKzgicf&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "Who was the first Black baseball player to integrate Major League Baseball?",
      "answer": "Jackie Robinson",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Satchel Paige", "Hank Aaron", "Babe Ruth"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/-VE0-ynbg4A?si=DE1Ikt1e2eUo1x34&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "What NBA player is nicknamed 'King James'?",
      "answer": "LeBron James",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Jordan", "Kobe Bryant", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/51CHNtNlFR8?si=fAkiAKXkDeh5RL0S&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "Which tennis star has won 23 Grand Slam singles titles?",
      "answer": "Serena Williams",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Venus Williams", "Naomi Osaka", "Roger Federer"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/C5ZDl4epfbM?si=VPhkiCa2LpUpSG-F&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "Who is the only Black quarterback to have won multiple Super Bowls?",
      "answer": "Patrick Mahomes",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Doug Williams", "Russell Wilson", "Tom Brady"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/hZFMyp3oJOs?si=-MP9rrBQ_uAjsdX-&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "What boxer was known as 'The Greatest' and 'The People's Champion'?",
      "answer": "Muhammad Ali",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Joe Frazier", "Mike Tyson", "Rocky Balboa"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/1lvkeUjEMlA?si=U6s8p7hc6tHTp5Tn&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "Who was the first Black woman to win an Olympic gold medal?",
      "answer": "Alice Coachman",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Wilma Rudolph", "Florence Griffith-Joyner", "Simone Biles"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/BvYQGMI00TY?si=bQStyL9f17D0SmxA&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "What team did Michael Jordan win six championships with?",
      "answer": "Chicago Bulls",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Washington Wizards", "Los Angeles Lakers", "New York Knicks"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/TrB20BZ454Y?si=HGs_LhJIrgKTn2Sw&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "Who became the first Black head coach to win a Super Bowl?",
      "answer": "Tony Dungy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Mike Tomlin", "Lovie Smith", "Bill Belichick"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/ySpyZVapr00?si=JYuXQYJH_hWri8fZ&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "What city is known as the birthplace of hip-hop?",
      "answer": "The Bronx",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Brooklyn", "Atlanta", "Detroit"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/10C-Q3NIlzU?si=Dl8-0wEqLUH4dxcb&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "Who founded FUBU, the iconic streetwear brand?",
      "answer": "Daymond John",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Russell Simmons", "Sean Combs", "Virgil Abloh"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/HrS06xpWCNE?si=jSi1ZrDbRaWEIcNj&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["fashion", "business"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "What artist painted the famous work 'Sugar Shack'?",
      "answer": "Ernie Barnes",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Jean-Michel Basquiat", "Kerry James Marshall", "Bob Ross"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/xnJGTPpQfW8?si=MHa6YB7i4PSC8CfK&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["art", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "Which Black author wrote 'The Bluest Eye' and 'Beloved'?",
      "answer": "Toni Morrison",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Maya Angelou", "Zora Neale Hurston", "Alice Walker"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/DlJl3vjs-KI?si=zDqpeWW-kv1UQ4hR&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "Who gave the famous 'I Have a Dream' speech?",
      "answer": "Martin Luther King Jr.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Malcolm X", "Barack Obama", "Frederick Douglass"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/uNskL7yDVlw?si=4rsu1F0VRtmYIhQg&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["history", "civil rights"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "What music festival celebrating Black culture was featured in 'Summer of Soul'?",
      "answer": "Harlem Cultural Festival",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Afropunk Festival", "Essence Festival", "Woodstock"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/wZ6mimBZ60w?si=hxldaJuBsRxaYcKI&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "What cultural movement in the 1920s centered around Black art, music, and literature?",
      "answer": "Harlem Renaissance",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Black Arts Movement", "Civil Rights Movement", "Jazz Age"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/9gboEyrj02g?si=rYK4n-08ume_u1Qn&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["history", "culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "What fashion designer became the first Black creative director at Louis Vuitton?",
      "answer": "Virgil Abloh",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Olivier Rousteing", "Telfar Clemens", "Dapper Dan"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/bzZsGeyg3Kw?si=kHnV7BNqIXhL6HIS&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["fashion", "business"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "Who wrote the book 'Between the World and Me'?",
      "answer": "Ta-Nehisi Coates",
      "incorrect_answers": ["James Baldwin", "Cornel West", "Richard Wright"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/QH2Rs105_o4?si=ql3DJz6yS48nh64G&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "What historical event inspired the film 'Judas and the Black Messiah'?",
      "answer": "The Assassination of Fred Hampton",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Montgomery Bus Boycott", "The Watts Riots", "The Harlem Riots"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Y8SuKKGl8Lo?si=oC-YhNgg7H6f_Y8X&amp;controls=0&amp;start=20",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["history", "film"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question": "'Some say the blacker the berry, the sweeter the juice. I say the darker the flesh then the deeper the roots...' are lyrics by which legendary Hip-hop artist?",
      "answer": "2Pac",
      "incorrect_answers": ["LL Cool J", "Dr. Dre", "The Notorious B.I.G."],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/IYF3ULLDb6Y?si=I5HYDOkTkyCEAMv0&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture", "hip-hop"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question": "Who played the character Wakanda's Queen Mother in 'Black Panther'?",
      "answer": "Angela Bassett",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Viola Davis", "Lupita Nyong'o", "Halle Berry"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/dhjfM4RHpGA?si=YZjvQvgANyKM4S-a&amp;controls=0&amp;start=60",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question": "Which artist is famous for the song 'Alright', which became an anthem for the Black Lives Matter movement?",
      "answer": "Kendrick Lamar",
      "incorrect_answers": ["J. Cole", "Drake", "Childish Gambino"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z-48u_uWMHY?si=QSNVKDx-FutaAa0v&amp;controls=0&amp;start=160",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question": "What actress starred as Annalise Keating in the TV show 'How to Get Away with Murder'?",
      "answer": "Viola Davis",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kerry Washington", "Taraji P. Henson", "Regina King"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Sce_K-dMjfE?si=vuH5SIaAtJEP4XWT&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "drama"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question": "Who was the first Black person to win an EGOT (Emmy, Grammy, Oscar, and Tony)?",
      "answer": "Whoopi Goldberg",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Oprah Winfrey", "Harry Belafonte", "Sidney Poitier"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/QBPzkjJQE3c?si=HivmA4HJdv9x-_Es&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["history", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question": "What comedian is known for the stand-up special 'Bigger & Blacker'?",
      "answer": "Chris Rock",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Dave Chappelle", "Eddie Murphy", "Kevin Hart"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/tgHcYxKjwVE?si=FBqiDgTlnXE3d2NI&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["comedy", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question": "What film stars Beyoncé as Deena Jones in a story inspired by the Supremes?",
      "answer": "Dreamgirls",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Color Purple", "Cadillac Records", "Sparkle"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/PLp9i3aIbeU?si=9Q5Y8EJOK_T8ba2L&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question": "Who became the first Black woman to win an individual gold medal at the Winter Olympics?",
      "answer": "Debi Thomas",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Gabby Douglas", "Serena Williams", "Alice Coachman"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/u5SiB6hu4UU?si=zC8Re9e1Ggvsf3er&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question": "What TV show featured the characters Tia Landry and Tamera Campbell?",
      "answer": "Sister, Sister",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Living Single", "Family Matters", "Girlfriends"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/qFZckPx7ZXg?si=AhlhfEDvomMQ7bib&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question": "Which athlete lit the Olympic cauldron at the 1996 Atlanta Games?",
      "answer": "Muhammad Ali",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Jordan", "Carl Lewis", "Jesse Owens"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/80wMMFAcweQ?si=jOGiH8X42ay_gZPj&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question": "Which artist is known for the song 'This Is America'?",
      "answer": "Childish Gambino",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Drake", "Kanye West", "J. Cole"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/VYOjWnS4cMY?si=yPOiCJeKEwmhJtsd&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question": "What is the name of the streaming platform Jay-Z once owned?",
      "answer": "Tidal",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Spotify", "Apple Music", "SoundCloud"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Revmkhxu7dk?si=9EqlU3E6Di6XpEUT&amp;controls=0&amp;start=41",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["business", "music"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question": "Which soul music legend sang the National Anthem at the 1983 NBA All-Star Game?",
      "answer": "Marvin Gaye",
      "incorrect_answers": ["James Brown", "Luther Vandross", "Aretha Franklin"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/NC-Jt58FbRc?si=c2NTW0TDOZH-E8sT&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["soul", "sports", "music"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question": "Which comedian is known for creating the sketch 'I'm Rick James, B****'?",
      "answer": "Dave Chappelle",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kevin Hart", "Chris Rock", "Eddie Murphy"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/GiOEgNuUpo4?si=a7CvrIwnXAoNsDCs&amp;controls=0&amp;start=5",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["comedy", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "question": "Which TV show featured Queen Latifah as Khadijah James?",
      "answer": "Living Single",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Girlfriends", "Sister, Sister", "Moesha"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/jnD2mdaxUAo?si=Cbvtij3p8GDpDwz_&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "question": "What 90s sitcom starred Brandy Norwood as the title character?",
      "answer": "Moesha",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Parkers", "Sister, Sister", "Girlfriends"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/5rqF--xeup8?si=G9-y-RmOdDKw6ZvV&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "question": "Who played Celie in the 1985 film 'The Color Purple'?",
      "answer": "Whoopi Goldberg",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Oprah Winfrey", "Viola Davis", "Halle Berry"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/zuj20RIdKHo?si=h8eay_CtIF9NA7gw&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "question": "Which rap group released the album 'Straight Outta Compton'?",
      "answer": "N.W.A.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Wu-Tang Clan", "Public Enemy", "Run-D.M.C."],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/c4rMYyEpstE?si=kO0-PiljPkEG3fL7&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "question": "Which Black filmmaker directed 'Do the Right Thing'?",
      "answer": "Spike Lee",
      "incorrect_answers": ["John Singleton", "Ava DuVernay", "Tyler Perry"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/yVAD4fYRcvA?si=ebLN0a4EjzTrjYXV&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "question": "Who was the first Black woman to appear on the cover of Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue?",
      "answer": "Tyra Banks",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Serena Williams", "Naomi Campbell", "Gabby Douglas"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/CvHqpkDBO94?si=mDmxRJgSXBFLuLlz&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["sports", "fashion"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "question": "Who wrote and performed the spoken word poem 'Still I Rise'?",
      "answer": "Maya Angelou",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Toni Morrison", "Nikki Giovanni", "Alice Walker"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/qviM_GnJbOM?si=w0v8QxHwgVM0HJdl&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "question": "What is the name of the debut album by Lauryn Hill?",
      "answer": "The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Unplugged", "Fugees Forever", "Songs in A Minor"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/T6QKqFPRZSA?si=Wh9-DmlpXxR-ZvI9&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "question": "Who portrayed Storm in the original X-Men movie series?",
      "answer": "Halle Berry",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Angela Bassett", "Zoe Saldana", "Taraji P. Henson"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/NTUZYeoWtBs?si=KxmBUZNu4DboLkVA&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "question": "Which Black scientist is known for his work with peanuts and agricultural science?",
      "answer": "George Washington Carver",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Percy Julian", "Mae Jemison", "Neil deGrasse Tyson"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/sdz8XTNttdc?si=cqfNFX4N1zriAhzS&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["science", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "question": "According to the song 'Cry For You' by Jodeci, how long has she been gone and is it too long?",
      "answer": "An Hour, Yes",
      "incorrect_answers": ["10 Hours, No", "7 Whole Days, Yes", "10 Minutes, No"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/Iznvc-eqKpU?si=uRT_Jp3Cwm9638k3&amp;controls=0",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "question": "Which artist created the album 'To Pimp a Butterfly'?",
      "answer": "Kendrick Lamar",
      "incorrect_answers": ["J. Cole", "Drake", "Childish Gambino"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "question": "What 90s sitcom starred Will Smith and has a dramatized reboot?",
      "answer": "The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Martin", "Family Matters", "Living Single"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "question": "Which Black playwright wrote 'A Raisin in the Sun'?",
      "answer": "Lorraine Hansberry",
      "incorrect_answers": ["August Wilson", "Zora Neale Hurston", "Toni Morrison"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "question": "What hip-hop group is known for the song 'Fight the Power'?",
      "answer": "Public Enemy",
      "incorrect_answers": ["N.W.A.", "Run-D.M.C.", "Beastie Boys"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "question": "Who is the first Black woman to win the Best Actress Oscar?",
      "answer": "Halle Berry",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Viola Davis", "Octavia Spencer", "Cicely Tyson"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "question": "Which actor portrayed Jackie Robinson in the film '42'?",
      "answer": "Chadwick Boseman",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Denzel Washington", "Michael B. Jordan", "Will Smith"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "question": "What is the name of the character played by Eddie Murphy in 'Beverly Hills Cop'?",
      "answer": "Axel Foley",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Billy Ray Valentine", "Prince Akeem", "Reggie Hammond"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "comedy"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "question": "Which athlete was the first Black man to win the Masters Tournament?",
      "answer": "Tiger Woods",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Lee Elder", "Calvin Peete", "Charlie Sifford"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["sports", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "question": "Who wrote the novel 'Their Eyes Were Watching God'?",
      "answer": "Zora Neale Hurston",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Toni Morrison", "Maya Angelou", "Alice Walker"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "question": "Which singer is known as the 'Empress of the Blues'?",
      "answer": "Bessie Smith",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Ella Fitzgerald", "Billie Holiday", "Nina Simone"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "question": "What is the name of Beyoncé's first solo studio album?",
      "answer": "Dangerously in Love",
      "incorrect_answers": ["B'Day", "4", "Lemonade"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "question": "Who played Detective Alonzo Harris in the movie 'Training Day'?",
      "answer": "Denzel Washington",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Samuel L. Jackson", "Laurence Fishburne", "Morgan Freeman"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "question": "Which author wrote 'The Souls of Black Folk'?",
      "answer": "W.E.B. Du Bois",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Frederick Douglass", "James Baldwin", "Ralph Ellison"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["literature", "history"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "question": "Which rap artist founded the record label Roc-A-Fella Records?",
      "answer": "Jay-Z",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Nas", "P. Diddy", "Dr. Dre"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "business"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "question": "Who was the first Black woman elected to the U.S. Congress?",
      "answer": "Shirley Chisholm",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Kamala Harris", "Barbara Jordan", "Condoleezza Rice"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["history", "politics"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "question": "What movie features the line 'You is kind, you is smart, you is important'?",
      "answer": "The Help",
      "incorrect_answers": ["12 Years a Slave", "Fences", "Precious"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "question": "Who directed the movie 'Selma'?",
      "answer": "Ava DuVernay",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Spike Lee", "Barry Jenkins", "Ryan Coogler"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "question": "Which Black superhero film was released in 1998, starring Wesley Snipes?",
      "answer": "Blade",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Spawn", "Steel", "Black Panther"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "question": "What sitcom featured Jaleel White as Steve Urkel?",
      "answer": "Family Matters",
      "incorrect_answers": ["The Fresh Prince of Bel-Air", "Martin", "Sister, Sister"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "question": "What is the name of the iconic Black fashion magazine founded in 1945?",
      "answer": "Ebony",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Essence", "Jet", "Black Enterprise"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["fashion", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "question": "Which actress played Foxy Brown in the 1974 film?",
      "answer": "Pam Grier",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Cicely Tyson", "Diahann Carroll", "Aretha Franklin"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["film", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "question": "Which athlete is known as 'The Black Mamba'?",
      "answer": "Kobe Bryant",
      "incorrect_answers": ["LeBron James", "Michael Jordan", "Shaquille O'Neal"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["sports", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "question": "Who sang the song 'Respect', which became an anthem for civil rights and feminism?",
      "answer": "Aretha Franklin",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Nina Simone", "Ella Fitzgerald", "Diana Ross"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "question": "Which actress starred in the TV series 'Scandal' as Olivia Pope?",
      "answer": "Kerry Washington",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Viola Davis", "Regina King", "Taraji P. Henson"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["television", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "question": "What album is considered a classic by the rap group A Tribe Called Quest?",
      "answer": "The Low End Theory",
      "incorrect_answers": ["Enter the Wu-Tang (36 Chambers)", "Illmatic", "Doggy Style"],
      "content": "",
      "content_type": "",
      "category": ["music", "history"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "question": "But Black Dynamite...",
      "answer": "...I sell drugs to the community.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["...ain't nobody messing with my kung fu skills!","...the orphans need their cereal!","...justice never takes a day off!"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/l4-8eh3caY0?si=g8UJRrltp_juZjRH&amp;start=175",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["comedy", "pop culture", "film"],
      "challenge": 2
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "question": "Hey Dirty!...",
      "answer": "...baby, I got your money!",
      "incorrect_answers": ["...don't you mess with my style!","...shimmy shimmy ya!","...your reputation precedes you!"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/XXTzm5GtqVo?si=Bb9A1q0dluPl7VDJ&amp;start=198",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "comedy", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "question": "I started thinking to myself...",
      "answer": "...Man, what did he do to make them ni**as that mad?",
      "incorrect_answers": ["...What if this is exactly where I'm supposed to be?","...Am I the drama?","...Did these fools eat all the cereal?"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/A6Tzg0tTJ1Y?si=xw0O8jDn_zrsLtg5&amp;start=18",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["comedy", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "question": "Before I let you...",
      "answer": "...go",
      "incorrect_answers": ["...leave","...down","...walk away"],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/y4854yQ1sHc?si=taUdA0zugxbip7K7&amp;start=125",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "pop culture", "soul"],
      "challenge": 1
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "question": "I can't leave you alone...",
      "answer": "...you got me feenin'.",
      "incorrect_answers": ["...because I love you.","...you got me going.","...but I'll try."],
      "content": "https://www.youtube.com/embed/eB6pGn2UK2U?si=zE38dciqyXEp6fAA&amp;start=114",
      "content_type": "youtube_video",
      "category": ["music", "R&B", "pop culture"],
      "challenge": 2
    }
  ]
  